Guide to the Henri Chopin Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Material, 1957-2007; Series VII; 15.62; (46 boxes) + 3 objects
  - Sound Recordings
    - Audiocassettes, commercially released and non-commercial
      - Works by others, unsorted, (34 audiocassettes)
        - Seuphor, Michel., undated; 1; 00:42:22; Static can be heard on the tape. Audio on the left channel is recorded at a lower volume from 42:23 until the end of the tape. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507489)
        - Helyer, Nigel. "Siren Song", 1992; 1; 00:29:51 (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507497)
        - De Vree, Paul. "poemi audio-visuali', 1970; 1; 00:26;05; Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507505)
        - Singh, Gary. "Works with Jerks", 1992-1994; 1; 00:49:57 (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507513)
          "My Name is Not Ed"
          "TORNtables"
          "Kataklysmos"
          "Problems of Ambience"
          "The Fugitive"
        - Meyer, Peter R. "Nattövning / Ektoplasma", undated; 1; 01:03:00; Audio sounds unclear at times on the tape. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507521)
        - Hammersley and Tabor. "The 4-Day Opportunity", 1981; 1; 01:00:57; The program is distorted at times. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507539)
          A Theory of Dancing
          W --__(h)
          [Roem] Studies Volume 1
          Loam
        - A poem by H. Chopin / Akenaton...The bio, undated; 1; This audiocassette is blank. The tape has not been digitized. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507547)
        - Paté de Voix 4, 1990; 1; 01:00:33; The program is distorted at times. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507554)
          Torino, gennaio
          Chopin, Henri. "Chuiantantes et Répits", 7' 42"
          Keppler, Joseph. "Percolator", 30"
          Keppler, Joseph. "Improvised Caesuras", 2' 45"
          Keppler, Joseph. "U.S.S. Ohio", 1' 50"
          Keppler, Joseph. "Timepiece", 15"
          Keppler, Joseph. "Communication", 1' 40"
          bpNichol. "senza titolo", 1' 40"
          byNichol. "senza titolo", 2' 27"
          bpNichol. "And this is what it means when meaning's over", 6' 40"
          Bouche, Thierry. (pour Bob & Nèv) "Tout électre", 2' 37"
          Heidsieck, Bernard. "Derviche / Le Robert" (Lettre "B"), 6'
          Valsher. "da 'autgedichte' ", 6' 42"
          Wendt, Larry. "Number 4", 8' 22"
          Bertola, C. and Vitacchio, A. "Adattarsi", 7' 35"
        - Damen, Herman. "verbosonies", 1970; 1; 00:33:59 (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507562)
        - Andersen, Eric. "The Crying Place", 1991 June 18 to 1991 July 13; 1; 01:03:20; Static can be heard on the tape. A high amount of hiss can be heard. The audio is sometimes unclear. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507570)
        - Sarenco. "political poems', 1970; 1; 00:18:59 (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507588)
          "Kein Gott" (1970)
          "Papa Zum" (1968-1970)
          "Homage to Lin Piao (1970)
          "Bisturi Poem" (1970)
          "Screditare Le Autorità Borghesi!" (1970)
        - "Audio Eyes", 1983; 1; 01:31:24; The program is distorted at times. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507596)
        - Rothenberg, Jerome. New Wilderness Audiographics, 1977; 1; 00:37:36 (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507604)
        - Word Theatre Soundpoetry, 1965-1995; 1; 01:27:57; The program is distorted at times. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507612)
          International Exhibition in Koenigsberg
          1. Scherstjanoi, Valeri, Horn, Ernest and Czukay, Holger. "Das Radio Der zukunft"
          2. Claus, Carlfriedrich. "Lautaggregat"
          3. Kolomijtsev, Andrei. "Asphaltstrasse"
          8. Dutton, Paul. "Stereo Head" and "Kit-Talk"
          9. Bulatov, Dmitry. "Russian Folk Noism" and "Life with machine"
          10. Riedl, Josef Anton. "Vielleicht ist es so" and "Paper Musik II"
          11. Chopin, Henri. Dialogue
          12. Mon, Franz. "Montage aus "artikulationen 62"
          13. Vinogradov, German, Kravchenko, Alexsei, and Meinkov, Willi R. "Kwakuum"
          14. Hutchinson, Brenda. "Long Tube Trio"
          15. Cobbing, Bob. "From ABC to Sound (d-p-t)"
        - Meyer, Peter R. Nattövning/P, 1982 June; 1; 00:32:52; The program is distorted at times. Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507620)
        - Bissett, Bill. "Northern Birds in Color", undated; 1; 01:00:36; The program is distorted at times. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507638)
          "hunee sound chant"
          "his vois was going out uv nim"
          "jed bi kor bensk trik"
          "how uy know"
          "riff th veil from my eyes"
          "ther may have bin a tunnel"
          "in yr life"
          "alpha"
          "awake in th red desert"
          "wand ring"
          "normal is not returning"
          "th magic lure uv sea shells"
          "sound chant"
          "farrago 79"
          "th centr is th belly button"
          "victoria si eeee:"
          "th lifting hands"
          "th wun with th glasses"
          "th unicorn is loos"
          "i gotta feelin"
          "chant"
          "collingwood"
          "Yu want to walk with me (asking) may all thees blessings"
          "england scotland nd wales"
          "blew horizon"
          "hunee chant..."
        - Gruppo 70. "poemi tecnologici", 1965-1971; 1; 01:00:35; Static can be heard on the tape. Audio in the right channel was recorded at a lower volume. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507646)
          Marcucci, Lucia. "poesia auditiva"
          Miccini, Eugenio. "concerto per armi, vox humana a varia tecnologia"
          Ori, Luciano. "situazione bianca PTF-1"
          Perfetti, Michele. "poema inglobante"
          Pignotti, Lamberto. "il re dei pagliacci"
        - Bak, Eleonore. Ton Arbeiten, "Ohne Titel", 1987; 1; 00:12:57 (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507653)
        - Supranormal, 1983; 1; 00:53:35; The program is distorted at times. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507661)
          A list of contents on the audiotape are included. Side two is attributed to Lee Harwood.
          1. Editorial/Introduction
          2. Brown, Paul. "Startled"
          3. Sheppard, Robert G. "The Lover"
          4. Woods, Greg. "The Lemon Blossom and the Cat"
          5. Chopin, Henri. "Throat Power"
          6. Row, John. "Judas Poe M"
          7. Griffiths, Bill. "Found Texts"
          a. "Found Text on Rochester"
          b. "Found Text"
          c. "Found Sea Texts"
          d. "Ode to Autumn"
          8. Henri, Adrian. "Mrs. Albion You've Got a Lovely Daughter"
          1. "Chen"
          2. "Animal Days"
          3. "Triangulation of Points A, B, C."
          4. "Portraits 1-4"
          5. "Boston Spring"
          6. "Quasida"
          7. "The Long Black Veil (Book Six)" and "Three Trans-Tristan Tzara"
          8. "Approach"
          9. "For Robert Desnos"
          10. "Good Time 2"
        - Rühm, Gerhard. "Wintermärchen", 1976 December; 1; 00:17:47 (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507679)
        - McCaffery, Steve. "research on the mouth", 1977-1978; 1; 00:58:44; Static can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507687)
          "S.I.S.M.A." (Movements 1 & 2)
          "Portraits 1-34"
          "S 1 Z 2 Z 1 E 1 R 2 Z 3"
          "Names for Cricket"
          "Structure of Incident"
          "A Little Valentine"
          "Pleasant Ode for Vincent Trasov"
          "S.I.S.M.A." (Movement 3)
          "Aupe Relationships"
          "Black Aleph" (1 & 2)
        - Collin, Françoise and Seyrig, Delphine. "Anne, Ma Soeur Anne", 1973?; 1; 01:26:45 (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507695)
        - Nitsch, Hermann. Orgelkonzert, 1986 December 9; 1; 01:03:08 (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507703)
          A list of contents are included with this audiocassette.
          "die geburt des dionysos"
          "die tiefe des alls"
          "die tiefe des alls (Forsetzung)"
          "der hirschgott"
          "dornenkrönung"
        - Mac Low, Jackson. "Homage to Leona Bleiweiss", 1977; 1; 01:02:31; Static can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507711)
          New Wilderness Audiographics
        - Dana, Llys and Marlow, Jack. "Court Circuit", undated; 1; 00:18:51 (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507729)
        - Chopin, Henri. "Le Voyage Labio - Velaire" / "Le Cri", 1971 August - September; 1; 00:15:58; The program is distorted at times. Audio in the right channel is silent from 00:05-01:09 and again at the end of the program. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507737)
        - Taliesin and Dana, Llys. "Hautension" / "Alkaest", undated; 1; 01:00:35; The program is distorted at times. Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507745)
        - Flynt, Henry. "You Are My Everlovin'" / "Celestial Power", 1980-1981; 1; 01:27:52; The program is distorted at times. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507752)
        - Flynt, Henri. "You Are My Everlovin'" / "Celestial Power", 1980-1981; 1; 01:28:01; The program is distorted at times. Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507778)
        - Chopin, Henri. Poesie Sonore Internationale, undated; 1; 00:56:47 (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507760)
          Seuphor, Michel. "Tout en Roulant les RR" (1926)
          Seuphor, Michel. "Discours Politque" (1961)
          Dufréne, François. "Les Joyeux Sisyphe II" (1979)
          Heidsieck, Bernard. "Démocratie" (1977-78)
          Chopin, Henri. "Le Parlement Européan" (1971)
          de Vree, Paul. "Magdalena, Appassionata, Lettervrouw" (1956, 1958, 1960)
          Novak, Ladislav. "Deux poèmes onomatopées" (1961, 1962)
          Gysin, Brion. "Junk is no good baby" (1960)
          Mon, Franz. "Ja-Nein-Parabel" (1971/78)
          Rühm, Gerhard. "Spricht 'über' Auditive Poesie" (1977)
          Jandl, Ernst. "Vom Lautgedicht" (1977)
          Lora-Totino, Arrigo. "'Smoke Words' for H. Chopin" (1978)
          Giorno, John. "Raspberry" (1976)
          Hanson, Sten. "The Glorious Desertion" (1969)
        - Seuphor, Michel., undated; 1; 00:42:09; The program is distorted at times. Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507786)
          "Poème Modèle", 1926
          "Poème 131", 1927
          "Pour la St Spinoza", 1978
          "Pour la St Oiseau", 1978
          "Le nageur", 1960
          "Falamagre", 1963
          "Comme le temps passe", 1962
          "Les vieux amis", 1963
          "Le Rossignol", 1964
          "Fidèle à l'amour du jeu", 1973
          "La Puste", 1972
          "Investiture", 1973
          "Un résumé de tout", 1973
          "Communiqué", 1958
          Servir la Poésie", 1958
          "Le nouveau-né", 1962
          "Curriculum", 1972
          "Lentement", 1960
          "Prière sur l'Acropole", 1962
        - Chopin, Henri. Poesie Sonore Internationale, undated; 1; 00:57:10 (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507794)
      - Works by others, unsorted, (35 audiocassettes)
        - Fontana, Giovanni., undated; 1; 00:53:17 (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104507927)
          1. Radio / Dramma 58
          2. Radio / Dramma 35 / III
          3. Radio / Dramma 37
          4. Radio / Dramma 7 / II
          5. "Code"
          6. Da "Primavera/Acquario"
          1. Pagine Da Radio / Dramma
          2. Tarocco / Meccanico
          3. Radio / Dramma 58 A
          4. Radio / Dramma 3
          5. Radio / Dramma 64
          6. Dalla Trasmis - Sione Radio: "Il Colpo Di Glottide"
        - Pisek, Bruno. "Liederzyklus", circa 1990; 1; 00:17:18 (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104507935)
        - Landy, Leigh. pour Henri Chopín bravo!, 1973-1980; 1; 01:18:53; Audio in the left channel was recorded at a very low level from 18:55-23:21. (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104507943)
          Dolby, stéréo
          1. "What's Left" (1980)
          2. "Une Maniere de Faire Le-Que Faire?" (1974)
          3. "La Phase" (1973)
          4. "Ambiguite" (1973)
          5. "Regiones Vocales" (1973)
        - Arcand, P. A. Music Gallery / Voix Virtuelles, 1992 March 19; 1; 00:59:00; Static can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104507950)
        - Chopin, Henri. A. C. R., 1987 March 22; 1; 00:55:58 (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104507968)
        - Chopin, Henri. Les 9 Saintes-Phonics, 1987; 1; 00:33:49 (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104507976)
        - Delajorka. "L'Vomo de si scaiveva addono", undated; 1; 00:16:04 (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104507984)
        - Meyer, Peter R. Nattövning, 1982 June; 1; 00:36:30 (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104507992)
        - Dutton, Paul. Full Throatle, 1998-06-23; 1; 00:40:48 (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104508008)
          "Stereo Head" (4:50)
          "Aurora" (7:00)
          "Wolf Chant" (3:19)
          "Mercure" (6:02)
          "Kit-talk" (1:53)
          "For the Letter That Begins Them All, H" (3:13)
          "Smile" (1:07)
          "Score for Tony, 1st Movement" (1:22)
          "Borealis" (6:57)
          "Northern Lights" (3:42)
        - Olsen, Peter. "Og Re Laks", 1987; 1; 00:15:00 (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104508016)
          1. "Nama Namen"
          2. "Siger T"
          3. "Huset er gult"
          4. "Hymne til mødremålene"
          5. "Mig og min dør er træe"
          6. "Uden titel"
          7. "Dickens, Butler og Woody jam"
          8. "uuuu"
          9. "Hello this is your captain speaking"
          1. "Siger O & Der kom en mand"
          2. "Langefinger"
          3. "Charlottenlund"
          4. "nik-nik nik-nik"
          5. "Virrende dæk"
          6. "Autostrada poesi"
          7. "To piger på en lang vej"
          8. "hididi plyh"
          9. "Alt for damerne"
        - Sarenco-Verdi A.I.P.S. Ensemble. "San Remando", 1979; 1; 00:37:52; The program is distorted at times. (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104508024)
          "Canta primavera"
          "Paloma negra"
          "Io bevo"
          "Yvonne"
          "Trieste mia-Tristezze di Chopin"
          "Troppo tardi"
          "Madonna clara"
        - Chopin, Henri. "le voyage labio - velaire / "le cri", 1971 August - September; 1; 00:15:55 (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104508032)
        - Merante, Angelo and Sonorika, Inika. "ompo kema", 1990; 1; 00:03:35; Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104508040)
        - Paté de Voix 3, 1987 March; 1; 01:02:27 (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104508057)
          Torino; Interpretazioni Sonore Di Poesia
          "Route One"
          "Riverrun"
          "Vowels"
          "Vowels lesson"
          "Emeralopia"
          "Route two"
          "Reel"
          "Hence"
        - Vonna-Michell, E.E. "Orange Wipes", 1979; 1; 00:06:10; This tape is a continuous loop. A note also reads: due to the nature of this cassette, any attempts to fast forward or rewind may result in irreparable damage. (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104508065)
          A liner note accompanying this audiocasette reads: This recording contains the third transcript of the orange wipes transcribed on October 12, 1979 by mounting five mono record heards, in the left and right hands and feet and dancing over and over some 900 feet of one-inch 16th century dance recordings braided to size a very small area.
        - Sarenco. "La poésie, on aime!" pour ou er H. Chopin, 1988; 1; 00:23:02; The program is distorted at times. (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104508073)
        - Momo Vol. 1, 1996; 1; 01:33:11; The program is distorted at times. (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104508081)
          This may be a commercial audiocassette.
        - Paté de Voix 5, 1990 January; 1; 01:02:13; The program is distorted at times. Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104508099)
          Torino, Interprétazioni Sonore Di Poesia
          "Darkness", 8' 25"
          "Uno Due Tre", 5' 10"
          "Lui sorride", 3' 20"
          "DeComposizione", 4' 40"
          "That's love my dear", 6' 50"
          "Adattarsi", 7' 15"
          "Walkabout One", 6' 50"
          "Walkabout Two", 8' 54"
          "Keybowords" (to Henri Chopin), 7' 10"
        - George, Glenda and Griffiths, Bill. Lobby Newsletter 17, 1981; 1; 00:23:11; The program is distorted at times. A high amount of hiss can be heard on the tape. (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104508107)
          "taut thought"
          "2 romany songs after borrow"
          "lurking tout près de moi"
          "no good variations on a newoastle song"
        - Paté de Voix 2, 1986 June; 1; 01:02:40; The program is distorted at times. (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104508115)
          Torino, Interpretazioni Sonore Di Poesia
          1. "Il"
          2. "Il Silenzio delle Sirene"
          3. "Canto"
          4. "Egli Il"
          5. "Esse"
          6. "Racconto Cinque"
          7. "Gli Occhi di Ulisse"
          1. "Doors"
          2. "Remote Control"
          3. "Hommage à Arthur Pétronio"
          4. "Annotations to Hamlet"
          5. "Homage to Alvin Lucier"
          6. "Annotations to Macbeth"
        - Battier, Marc. "Toca", 1993 September 12; 1; 00:09:15 (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104508123)
        - Reese, Marshall and Malone, Kirby. "Duo O Accident", 1978 July 23; 1; 00:46:19; A high amount of hiss can be heard on the tape. (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104508131)
          Introduction (Malone)
          what whole wheat means (Malone) and the winter rose (Reese)
          Click Poems (Mason)
          wrench wrench (Malone)
          59 (Reese)
          hallu voo (Malone)
          story (Reese)
          slugs (Reese)
          Dudu Pukwana the Saxophone (Mason)
          [ ] [ ] (Reese)
          phr (Malone)
        - Chopin, Henri. Poesie Sonore Internationale, undated; 1; 00:56:48 (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104508149)
        - Audiografika, 1989 March; 1; 01:03:45; The program is distorted at times. (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104508156)
          Riedl, Josef -Anton. "Vielleicht ist es so" and "Für Trommeln"
          Heidsieck, Bernard. "Der Viche / Le Robert, lettres 'L' & 'M'"
          Chopin, Henri. "Plurality I. I. I. I."
          Scherstjanoi, Valeri. "Sa-um"
        - Bak, Eleonore. "Ton Arbeiten", 1985-1987; 1; 00:26:29; Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104508172)
        - Froissements et Fractures De L'Air, 1985; 1; 00:14:16; The program is distorted at times. (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104508180)
        - "Culte De La Nature", 1986 September; 1; 01:01:21; The program is distorted at times. (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104508198)
          Komintern, Yaset. (Hommage au Maire de Tours), 1' 50"
          Roquin, Louis. "Le Vent" Trompette Solo, 3' 10"
          Metail, Michele. "Ethnopoeme" Nº2, 2'
          Sud, Riki. "Citè Maraux 96", 2' 55"
          Frontier, Alain, 5'
          Cahen, Jacqueline (Chant et Synthe), 6' 40"
          Hubaut, Joel, 1' 45"
          Pavl, Al (Decoration ou Peinture), 6' 55"
        - Ah ow HURT!, undated; 1; 00:47:42 (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104508206)
          "it is finished from beginning to end"
          "as it was found in writing"
        - The Tape Issue / Poets. Painters. Composers. No. 4, 1996; 1; 00:56:30 (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104508214)
        - Seuphor, Michel., 1979 October; 1; 00:42:05 (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104508222)
          "Poème 132", 1927
          "Poème 111", 1927
          "Tout en roulant les RR", 1927
          "Sinnge sannge", 1929
          "Erreur Brevetée", 1929
          "Cartes sur table", 1963
          "Discours Politique", 1962
          "Chant Toltèque", 1963
          "Langue vivante", 1963
          "Maille hillilil", 1962
          "Chanson de la dernière chance", 1966
          "Chanson de la fatalité", 1966
          "Chanson porte-chance", 1966
          "Pour la St Socrate", 1978
          "Pour la St Erasme", 1978
          "Servir la Poésie", 1958
        - Burt, Warren and Stewart, Amanda. "Collaboration" / "Some Poems", 1981-1987; 1; 00:41:01 (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104508230)
          A list of poems under the Amanda Stewart's "Some Poems" are included with the audiocassette. This audiocassette also notes it is for Henri Chopin.
          "Some Poems"
          1. •, 1985
          2. The War Poem, 1984
          3. I Mean, 1981
          4. Icon, 1982
          5. • Romance, 1981
          6. It Becomes, 1981-07
          7. The Truth About Bisexuality, 1983
        - Inter K-7, 1987; 1; 01:32:29; The program is distorted at times. (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104508248)
          Barteaux, David. "Hip Hop", 2:40
          Fekner, John and Summer, Sasha. "BD Cycles", 1:40
          Boisvert, Yves and Roy, Mike. "La Dima Tiva: je suis le nom que je porte", 2:33
          Hubaut, Joel., 2:04
          Orlan. "Ceci est mon corps, ceci est mon logiciel", 1:39
          Stirneman, Manfred. Score for "three Feedbacks and one lie", 2:24
          Arcand, Pierre-André. "Rire construit", 2:00
          Fontana, Giovanni. "Utricolo/Sacculo", 1:36
          Szka'Rosi, Endre and Konnektor RT. "Still Europe", 2:14
          Les Boubous. TV Hebdo, 2:16
          Develay, Frederic. "Le texte non lu...", 1:48
          Pavl, Al. "Symptôme 199.999: document", 2:03
          Heidsieck, Bernard. "La lettre p", 2:44
          Neveu, Angeline and Berrocal, Jac., 1:34
          Gagnon, Jean-Claude. "Un poète tout blanc, ayant tombé du'un rocher, se mit à chanter des mantras comme un vrai poète", 2:43
          Cantsin, Monty. "Rat Life", 1:56
          Saint-Onge, Michel. "Bête de langage", 1:54
          Robertson, Clive. Utilisation par le public de son installation sonore présentée au LIEU, 2:01
          Azzaria, Georges., 1:11
          Blake, Ian. "Hello Darling", 0:45
          Rose, Peter. Introduction to the "Pleasures of the Text", 2:50
          Vec and Summers, Rod. "Ulysse's dog", 2:13
          Adlers, Bengt. "Écrire Kierkegaard", 0:54
          Roffi, Gian Paolo. "Point d'interrogation", 0:50
          Dreyfus, Charles. "C'est interminable", 2:02
        - Wendt, Larry. "Guided Missile Favorites", 1988; 1; 01:03:08 (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104508255)
          1. "Teaching the Cat to Play the Guitar", 7' 39"
          2. "San Jose Sunrise", 3' 10"
          3. "San Jose Hot Spell", 10' 41"
          4. "Let's Go Down to the New Mall", 10' 1"
          1. "Ants", 5' 10"
          2. "Land of a Thousand Dentists", 6' 35"
          3. "Rude Awakenings", 8' 50"
          4. "Desparate", 7' 19"
          5. "Someone's at the Goddamned Door Again", 3' 48"
        - Concierto de Campanas Sacra Lucus, 1991 June 8; 1; 00:39:59 (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104508263)
        - L'Aiguille A Drecou, 1986 December; 1; 01:02:24 (Box 71, Item barcode 39002104508271)
      - Works by other, unsorted
        - "Antologia" / "Polipoetica", undated; 1; 01:03:24 (Box 80, Item barcode 39002104507802)
        - Audiografika, 1989; 1; 01:03:43; Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 80, Item barcode 39002104507828)
          Riedl, Josef-Anton. "Vielleicht ist es so - lautkompostion"
          Riedl, Josef-Anton. "Für Trommein - für Sprechen
        - Thomas, Paul. Media-Space, undated; 1; 00:33:03 (Box 80, Item barcode 39002104507844)
          "This is the Way I See It"
          "I See Land"
          "A Realist View"
        - Poèmes de René Char, 1987 February 15; 1; 00:34:44 (Box 80, Item barcode 39002104507851)
          "Redonnez leur"
          "Jacquemard et Julia"
          "Ibrium"
          "A une ferveur belliqueuse"
          "Réception d'Orion"
          "Les premiers instants"
          "A ma femme endormie"
          "Liberté"
          "Rémanence"
          "Se réchauffer l'ardeur"
          "L'alouette"
          "Les invenieurs"
          "Joue el dors"
          "A***"
          "Faction du muet"
          "Toute vie"
          "Faim rouge"
          "Le bouge de l'historien"
          "Evadné"